<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications on Ling-Jyh Chen</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/</link><description>Recent content in Publications on Ling-Jyh Chen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 23:00:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cclljj.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Journal Articles</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/journal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/journal/</guid><description>Chia-Yu Lo, Min-Te Sun, Ling-Jyh Chen, Kazuya Sakai, and Wei-Shinn Ku. Recurrent Learning on PM2.5 Prediction Based on Clustered Airbox Dataset. Accepted and to appear in IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering. Yi-Fang Chiang, Ka-Ui Chu, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Yao-Hua Ho. Predicting Risk of COVID-19 Outbreak by using Outdoor Air Pollution Indicators and Population Flow with Queueing Theory. Atmosphere, volume 13, issue 10, article number 1727, 2022. Jia-Hong Tang, Bo-Cheng Lin, Jing-Shiang Hwang, Ling-Jyh Chen, Bing-Sheng Wu, Hong-Lian Jian, Yu-Ting Lee, and Ta-Chien Chan.</description></item><item><title>Conference Papers</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/conference/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/conference/</guid><description>Fang-Jing Wu, Yudong Zhao, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Adaptive Creation and Migration of Time-Series City Profiles Based on Edge Computing. IEEE International Symposium on Personal, Indoor and Mobile Radio Communications (PIMRC'21), Virtual Conference, 2021. Dong-Yi Wu, Chen-I Huang, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Sound Recognition for City Soundscape: using Traffic Noise as an Example. IEEE International Conference on Technologies and Applications of Artificial Intelligence (TAAI'20), Taipei, Taiwan, 2020. (Domestic Track Best Paper Award) Ting-Hui Chiang, Yan-Ann Chen, Chun-Ting Chang, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Yu-Chee Tseng.</description></item><item><title>Posters/Demo</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/posters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/posters/</guid><description>Chia-Chin Chung, Chu-Chi Pai, Fu-Shiang Ching, Chao Wang, and Ling-Jyh Chen. When Post-Quantum Cryptography Meets the Internet of Things: An Empirical Study. ACM Conference on Embedded Networked Sensor Systems (ACM SenSys'22), Portland, Oregon, USA, 2022. Sheng-Chun Wu, Dong-Yi Wu, Fu-Hsiang Ching, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Participatory Sound Meter Calibration System for Mobile Devices. ACM Conference on Embedded Networked Sensor Systems (ACM SenSys'20), Yokohama, Japan, 2020. Yao-Hua Ho, Pei-En Li, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Yu-Lun Liu.</description></item><item><title>Book Chapters</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/chapters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/chapters/</guid><description>Ling-Jyh Chen and Ting-Kai Huang. Effective File Transfer in Mobile Opportunistic Networks. Mobile Opportunistic Networks: Architectures, Protocols and Applications (ISBN: 1420088122), pp 203-223, Mieso Denko (Ed.), Auerbach Publications, May 2011. Kuan-Ta Chen, Chien-Wei Lin, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Irwin King. Human Computation Games and Optimization of Their Productivity. Web Intelligence and Intelligent Agents (ISBN: 978-953-7619-85-5), pp 289-304, Zeeshan-Ul-Hassan Usmani (Ed.), InTech, March 2010. Ling-Jyh Chen, Li-Ping Tung, Tony Sun, and Nia-Chiang Liang.</description></item><item><title>Technical Reports</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/trs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/trs/</guid><description>J. W. S. Liu, E. T. H. Chu, J. M. Ho, L. J. Chen, S.-W. Bai, Y.-C. Chen, Y.-J. Lin, &amp;amp; J. Su. BeDIPS: A Building/environment Data Based Indoor Positioning Service. Technical Report TR-IIS-15-001, Institute of Information Science, Academia Sinica, 2015. Cheng-Yu Lin, Hung-Chia Chen, Ying-Yu Chen, Wang-Chien Lee, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Compressing Trajectories Using Inter-Frame Coding. Technical Report TR-IIS-10-007, Institute of Information Science, Academia Sinica, 2010. Ling-Jyh Chen, Bo-Chun Wang, and Kuan-Ta Chen.</description></item><item><title>Patents</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/patents/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/patents/</guid><description>Polly Huang, Po-Yen Lin, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Jyh-How Huang, Operation Method and Radio Device for Controlling Power Switch of Radio Based on Moving Speed, US Patent 8,559,902, October 15, 2013. Polly Huang, Seng-Yong Lau, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Jyh-How Huang, System and Method for Time Synchronization, US Patent 8,384,590, February 26, 2013. Polly Huang, Po-Yen Lin, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Jyh-How Huang, 利用移動速度控制無線電開關之操作方法及其無線電設備 , Taiwan Patent I416411, November 21, 2013. Polly Huang, Seng-Yong Lau, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Jyh-How Huang, 時間同步裝置、系統及其方法 , Taiwan Patent I415497, November 11, 2013.</description></item></channel></rss>