<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications on Ling-Jyh Chen</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/</link><description>Recent content in Publications on Ling-Jyh Chen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 23:00:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cclljj.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Journal Articles</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/journal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/journal/</guid><description>Chia-Yu Lo, Min-Te Sun, Ling-Jyh Chen, Kazuya Sakai, and Wei-Shinn Ku. Recurrent Learning on PM2.5 Prediction Based on Clustered Airbox Dataset. Accepted and to appear in IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering.
Sachit Mahajan, Ming-Kuang Chung, Jenny Martinez, Yris Olaya, Dirk Helbing, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Translating citizen-generated air quality data into evidence for shaping policy. Humanities and Social Sciences Communications. volume 9, article 122, April 2022.</description></item><item><title>Conference Papers</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/conference/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/conference/</guid><description>Fang-Jing Wu, Yudong Zhao, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Adaptive Creation and Migration of Time-Series City Profiles Based on Edge Computing. IEEE International Symposium on Personal, Indoor and Mobile Radio Communications (PIMRC'21), Virtual Conference, 2021. Dong-Yi Wu, Chen-I Huang, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Sound Recognition for City Soundscape: using Traffic Noise as an Example. IEEE International Conference on Technologies and Applications of Artificial Intelligence (TAAI'20), Taipei, Taiwan, 2020. (Domestic Track Best Paper Award) Ting-Hui Chiang, Yan-Ann Chen, Chun-Ting Chang, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Yu-Chee Tseng.</description></item><item><title>Posters/Demo</title><link>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/posters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cclljj.github.io/publications/posters/</guid><description>Sheng-Chun Wu, Dong-Yi Wu, Fu-Hsiang Ching, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Participatory Sound Meter Calibration System for Mobile Devices. ACM Conference on Embedded Networked Sensor Systems (ACM SenSys'20), Yokohama, Japan, 2020. Yao-Hua Ho, Pei-En Li, Ling-Jyh Chen, and Yu-Lun Liu. Indoor Air Quality Monitoring System for Proactive Control of Respiratory Infectious Diseases. ACM Conference on Embedded Networked Sensor Systems (ACM SenSys'20), Yokohama, Japan, 2020. Nai-Cih Liou, Cyuan-Heng Luo, and Ling-Jyh Chen. Why is short time PM2.</description></item></channel></rss>